

PHAM PHU THAO



17/06/1995



Phuthao0303@gmail.com



0976.905.280

Career Objective

➤ With more than 4 years of experience as a data analyst as well as 2-year experience in financial analysis in the banking industry, I'm good at making data analysis as well as financial analyst reports. In the next 3 years, I want to become a Senior Finance Analyst Supervisor and manage my team.

Working Experiences

11/2020 - Present



FE CREDIT

Data Analyst Specialist

Duties:

- Build data and provide risk control indicators for the Underwriting department
- Support for checking and feedback on data quality on Pega system, Robo system.
- Build data performance and calculation bonus for employee results of Underwriting, Early Collection, Late call Collection departments
- Build the report on the ratio of cash disbursements to the total amount of disbursements tracked by the daily, monthly
- Using the SAS system to build reports for the departments
- Using the framework to automatically refresh data and loading data on the SAS system for existing reports
- In addition, working on the ad-hoc tasks assigned

10/2018 - 10/2020



NAM A BANK

Senior Financial Analyst

Duties:

- Using the SQL tool to query data related to deposit, loan, income, and cost.
- Analyzing data related to deposits, loans, return, cost, and income of the bank system to make the daily report.
- Analyzing data of capital structure and making analyst reports.
- Following and searching the KPI business of all business units in the Southwest region and making the report for these regions every month.
- Taking responsibility for making the report of the bank.
- Co-ordinating with business units to set up yearly KPI plans.
- Co-ordinating with the accounting department, credit department, project department, and finance department to make the jobs work effectively.
- Taking different requirements due to the command of my leader

04/2016 - 10/2018



SSI SECURITY COMPANY

Broker

Duties:

- Analyzing stock and choosing the stocks in the catalog through the filter
- Advising my customer in the stocks of a catalog
- Managing a stock category with nab 10 billion VND
- Analyzing data and market trends.
- Networking to attract potential clients

Education



09/2013 - 09/2017

University: BANKING UNIVERSITY

Major: BANKING AND FINANCE

Classification: **GOOD**

Activities

✓ The charitable activity: porridge at the hospital, gifts for the homeless

- ✓ The contest of scientific research
- ✓ Explore Saigon tour
- ✓ Play some sports: Volleyball, badminton, football,...